<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resume>
  <applicant>
    <name>McKayla Washburn</name>
    <phone>8016159924</phone>
    <email>partheseas@gmail.com</email>
    <website>https://mckay.la/</website>
  </applicant>
  <references>
    <person>
      <name>Shannon Lott</name>
      <phone>5036027401</phone>
    </person>
    <person>
      <name>Kent Huston</name>
      <phone>8018396549</phone>
    </person>
    <person>
      <name>Jennessa White</name>
      <phone>4352166382</phone>
    </person>
  </references>
  <experience>
    <job from="11/16" to="6/18">
      <position>Restaurant Manager</position>
      <company>Taco Bell</company>
      <city>Riverton, UT</city>
      <description>I was in charge of staffing new restaurant locations,
        as well as supervising contractors at the construction sites to ensure
        that the building and equipment met the necessary requirements to run
        the store optimally once they opened.</description>
    </job>
    <job from="8/16" to="11/16">
      <position>Training Coach</position>
      <company>Freddy's</company>
      <city>Draper, UT</city>
      <description>I primarily focused on hiring and training staff members to
        assist in the opening of several new locations during my time
        with Freddy’s.</description>
    </job>
    <job from="4/16" to="8/16">
      <position>Field Technician</position>
      <company>Alder</company>
      <city>Columbia, SC</city>
      <description>I was responsible for scheduling installation appointments,
        directing installations, and providing any necessary service to the
        security systems for customers. I also assisted in inventory at our
        warehouse, would provide support to other technicians on installations
        and services when necessary, and insured that all their installations
        were done properly.</description>
    </job>
    <job from="8/15" to="3/16">
      <position>Account Manager</position>
      <company>Vivint</company>
      <city>Lindon, UT</city>
      <description>I assisted in managing customer accounts, retention of current
        customers, resolving customer issues, insuring high quality customer service,
        and auditing to ensure accuracy, consistency of information on accounts,
        and accuracy of metrics measured by the company.</description>
    </job>
    <job from="3/12" to="8/15">
      <position>Assistant Manager</position>
      <company>Taco Bell</company>
      <city>Payson, UT</city>
      <description>I played a key role in the training and development of all of
        our employees and ensuring that our restaurant was as successful as possible.
        I was responsible for management of inventory and financial security,
        as well as oversight of the stores general operations. My store won
        several awards during my time there and I was often called upon to
        travel the other stores that were considered “problem children” by the
        company for periods of several weeks to resolve issues and give instruction
        for the management and crew to prevent further issues.</description>
    </job>
  </experience>
  <education>
    <school to="1/14" graduated="true">
      <name>Springville High School</name>
    </school>
    <school from="1/18" to="current">
      <name>Utah Valley University</name>
      <description>I’m currently about half way through the Bachelor of Computer
        Science program at UVU and have always been fascinated by computers. When
        I was in 7th grade I taught myself HTML, CSS and JavaScript, and by the
        end of high school I was contributing to open source projects on GitHub.
        I’ve been using Node.js since the 0.4.x branch when it was still just
        Ryan Dahl’s side project. I remember when they still used the old cloud
        logo and I know the API like the back of my hand. More recently I’ve
        also learned Python and C++.</description>
    </school>
  </education>
</resume>
